

### GIANNE RAYANDAYAN GRAPHIC DESIGNER/ILLUSTRATOR/UX DESIGNER

PORTFOLIO: GRAYANDAY.COM GRAYANDA17@GMAIL.COM 15103-386-4554



#### **EDUCATION**

**ABOUT ME** 



University of California, San Diego

I am a motivated, detail-oriented, and adaptable individual with a passion B.S. Cognitive Science w/ Specialization for communication and provocation through design. I effectively collaborate in Human Computer Interaction with designers, engineers, and clients to produce quality work in a timely manner. 2013-2017



#### **SKILLS**

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Premiere Pro

Unbounce

Processing

**MATLAB** 

HTML/CSS/Javascript



#### METHODS

Visual Design

Wireframing

Rapid Prototyping

User Research

Competitive Analysis

User Personas

User Flows

**Affinity Diagrams** 

Parallel Design

**EXPERIENCE** 



### Graphic Design Intern UCSD Revelle College

September, 2016-June 2017

- Collaborated with photographers and designers to create advertisements, logos, and print items for student events.
- Corresponded with UCSD Revelle College Administrative Staff and student leaders to facilitate projects from beginning to completion

### Designer / Video Editor Racebending.com

July 2017

 Compiled and edited footage of Racebending's Super Asian America Comic Con 2017 panel footage for viewing on racebending.com and youtube.com

 Designed in-video graphical content to highlight panel's keynote speakers on Asian-American representation in media

## UX Researcher UCSD Mental Wellness Needfinding Project

March 2016 - June 2016

- Directed team's needfinding research on various student groups to understand the complexity of mental health stigma among UCSD students.
- Derived conclusions from surveys, interviews, and observation by creating affinity diagrams and language analysis
- Assisted with writing team's Design Brief and presenting team's work

# Graphic/UX Designer Design Startup Project "Wonder Plates"

March 2017 - June 2017

- Conducted qualitative surveys and user testing to promote data driven design of a cultural meal prep service.
- Collaborated with team members to develop startup's branding and promotional materials
- · Directed and edited startup's promotional video

### Graphic Designer Political Design Project

Jan. 2017 - March 2017

- Worked with a team to create a provocative redesign of UCSD's Sun God Music Festival advertisement campaign to bring attention to issues of deteriorating student event quality
- Designed final advertisement posters and Facebook ad banners to increase traffic towards mock event site for petition signatures

#### Freelance Graphic Designer

December 2015 - Present

Created promotional posters and T shirt designs for various UCSD student organizations

 Created graphics for an android mobile app block-elimination game and worked with lead developer to incorporate graphics into game's implementation